{
    "question": "-Apa beda Auxilary &amp; Operator?    -Siapa penemu font Old English?\r\n -Kapan Bahasa Inggris masuk ke Indonesia?",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "gaktau ee kak bntar takcarikan yha<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "there-care-many-reasons-for-keeping-dogs-as-pete-in-the-city-area-554",
            "question": "There care many reasons for keeping dogs as Pete in the city area, but many peo- ple feel that keeping pet dogs should not be allowed In the city. Dogs are often not taken care properly. They are kept in small backyards and rarely taken for walks. They are left in the yard all day by themselves while the family rune work. Very little attention is given to the dog and it is not a very good life for it. It is no wonder why these dogs bark and disturb the neighbours and become a nuisance to the community.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 On the other hand, not all people treat their dogs this may and why should the peo- ple receive a lot of pleasure and enjoyment from dog's stifle'? Dogs can make a lonely person's life happy or make wonderful play- mate. It can also teach a child responsibility as they not only Potts lay with the dog, but also need to exercise, feed, and care for the dog.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 I feel that we should be allowed to keep dogs in the city, because ills is taken care of properly, dogs can be a great source of pleasure. As a child / used to enjoy playing and taking care of my pet. There is not greater loyalty a nelson can get than from a well-caned dog.\u00a0    1. Some people do not like the presence of pet dogs In their surroundings because ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are left in the yards\u00a0 \r\n(B) the dogs are often neglected \r\n(C) the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours \r\n(D) the dogs play with the owner's child \r\n(E) the dogs guard the security of the enyit onrnent\u00a0 \r\n\r\n2. The main idea of the last paragraph is ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) pet dogs are loyal animals \r\n(B) pet dogs are more loyal than humans \r\n(C) dogs can be a great source of pleasure \r\n(D) the writer has no objection to keeping dogs In the city \r\n(E) the writer used to play and took care of his pet when he was a child\u00a0 \r\n\r\n3. We can infer from the text that keeping pet dogs in the city will not cause any problem as long ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are amusing \r\n(B) the neighbours like having pet dogs \r\n(C) the dogs do not balk at the neighbours \r\n(D) the writer has succeeded in persuading the neighbours \r\n(E) its presence does not disturb the neighbourhood",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1.c.the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours<br>2.c.dogs can be a great source of pleasure<br>3.e.it&#039;s presence does not disturb the neighbourhood<br>ini menurut jawaban saya :)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-kalimat-pujian-responnya-tentang-memuji-keindahan-alam-me-798",
            "question": "buat kalimat pujian + responnya tentang memuji keindahan alam, memuji mother, father, granpa/ma, teacher, brother and sister, friend, best friend pet, your self",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Keindahan alam :<br>A: Wow! such a beautiful park.<br>B: Yea! i think so.<br><br>2. Teacher :<br>A: Thanks Miss jasmine! i understand it well than before.<br>B: Your welcome.<br><br>Semoga membantu :D",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Alam <br>A : Look at that beautiful lake !<br>B : Amazing<br>Mother<br>A : mom, you look pretty everytime !<br>B : thank you dear<br>Father\u00a0<br>A : Dad, you cook this ?<br>B : Yup.<br>A : waw, you can be a great chef<br>Grandpa<br>A: Grandpa, do you made this toys ?<br>B : yes, my dear<br>A : its look amazing !<br>Brother<br>A : Hey, you made this story ?<br>B: yup<br>A : Its so funny ! i love it<br>Teacher\u00a0<br>A : Sir, I never met a great teacher like you<br>B : thank you<br>friend :<br>A : Hey, you look pretty when you wear that dress<br>B : really ? thank you !<br>Best friend per<br>A : your cat is so cute.<br>B: Hahaha, yes, i know that<br>Yourself :<br>A : Hey, i look beautifull with this t-shirt !",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "berikan-5-kalimat-giving-instruction-312",
            "question": "Berikan 5 kalimat giving instruction",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "aku tulis dalam procedural text, how to make omelete<br>first,crack the eggs<br>after that beat the eggs<br>an then mix it with a salt or meat<br>after that cook it in a hot plate<br>finaly eat the eggs",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-jelaskan-secara-singkat-dan-jelas-pengertian-dari-report-t-269",
            "question": "Tolong jelaskan secara singkat dan jelas pengertian dari report teks",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Definition of Report<br>Report is a text which presents information about something, as it is. It is as a result of systematic observation and analysis<br><br>Generic Structure of Report<br>1. General classification: Stating classification of general aspect of thing; animal, public place, plant, etc which will be discussed in general<br>2. Description: Describing the thing which will be discussed in detail; part per part , customs or deed for living creature and usage for materials<br><br>Language Feature of Report<br>\u2022 Introducing group or general aspect<br>\u2022 Using conditional logical connection; when, so, etc<br><span>\u2022 Using simple present tense</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "report text adalah salah satu jenis teks yang masuk kategori \" factual text \"<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "5-kalimat-verbal-dalam-bahasa-inggris-610",
            "question": "5\u00a0kalimat verbal dalam\u00a0bahasa inggris?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "We play football every morning<br>I go to the market every sunday<br>She plays soccer with Ella<br>He goes to the library<br>She buys some books in the store<br>Semoga Membantu<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "their-motivationimprove-if-they-858",
            "question": "Their motivation...............(improve) if they..........................(kick) a goal during the first half",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "their motivation increases when the kick goal during the first half<br><br>kalau salah gak apa-apa ya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "boleh-minta-contoh-soal-dari-ungkapan-maksud-532",
            "question": "Boleh minta contoh soal dari ungkapan maksud?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Maksud -&gt; Idea or opinion<br><br>I think the best way to be expert in mathematics is by practicing everyday.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ada-yang-tau-contoh-berita-acara-serah-terima-pekerjaan-proyek-558",
            "question": "Ada yang tau contoh Berita Acara Serah Terima Pekerjaan (Proyek) dalam bahasa Inggris?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span><em>Handover Works (Project</em><span><em>)</em></span></span><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-kalimat-past-tense-menggunakan-used-to-712",
            "question": "Contoh kalimat past tense menggunakan used to",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "that scissors used my mom<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "contohnya : i used to studying at night<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "carilah-posisi-kata-yang-tidak-tepat-yang-digaris-bawahi-dan-jela-276",
            "question": "Carilah posisi kata yang tidak tepat yang digaris bawahi dan jelaskan mengapa kata itu tidak tepat disertai alasannya. soal :    1. a survey indicates that 'really shows' have attracted the higher proportion of tv viewers since the end of the last quarter of 2008.\r\n2. the giant panda whose is also know as the panda bear of the bamboo panda is almost extinct because the bamboo forests where it lives are destroyed.\r\n3. we are a leasing company. as many as 65% of our employees are posted in the marketing division. most of them are smart, talented, good look young men, who do not mind working ten hours a day, six days a week.\r\n4. A : i heard that you will go camping after the final test. will i go with you ? \r\nB : yes, but you should get permission from your parents.\r\n5. A : what does justin bieber like ?\r\nB : he is handsome. he has good voice.\r\nA : is that why so many girls like him so much ?\r\nB : we can't help it.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1.science<br>2.whose<br>3.are posted<br>4.will<br>5.him<br>menurus saya itu jawabannya.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "him,since,that,live,are posting<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}